One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Just remember that it was you who cast suspicion on my crew.
لا تنسي أنكِ شككتِ في طاقمي
Without mutual trust, we won't have each other's backs when fighting for our lives!
أنّى لأشخاص لا يثقون ببعضهم القتال معًا في معركة مميتة؟
Sparks of Rebellion
فتيل التمرد
Traf was fuming when he left!
غادر تراو غاضبًا
Shinobu went too far saying all that crap!
شينوبو تلك، كيف أمكنها قول ذلك؟
You do understand what set her off, right?
لكنك تتفهم سبب نفاد صبر شينوبو-تشان، صحيح؟
Kaido invaded her country and laid waste to everything she had ever known,
فرض كايدو سيطرته على هذه البلاد وأفسد حياتها
but she endured it for twenty years while waiting for the moment to fight back.
لكنها تحمّلت الأمر وانتظرت هذه اللحظة لعشرين سنة
Whatever. Even if Bepo and the others had blabbed about the plan, I wouldn't blame them.
حتى إن أخبرهم بيبو والبقية بالخطة، ما كنتُ لألومهم
Sure, I mean, you'd have talked.
لأنك كنتَ لتفعل ذلك، صحيح؟
I can say the same about you!
أظن أنكِ كنتِ لتخبريهم أيضًا
Torture, huh?
التعذيب؟
I'd last three seconds.
ربما سأتحمل لثلاث ثواني
Hold out longer, will you?!
تلك مدة قصيرة جدًّا
Get outta here!
غادروا
I have no business with any of you damn peasants!
لا أحتاج أن تعتنوا بي أيها الحثالة الوضيعون
What's going on? An angry shout seems out of place in Ebisu Town.
ماذا؟ شخص غاضب في بلدة إبيسو التي يملؤها الضحك دائمًا؟
You there, old bean-washing monster granny!
أزوكي = شيطان العجوز صانعة البازلاء في الأساطير اليابانية
Stop it!
توقف
They're new here. They arrived yesterday after fleeing the capital.
إنهم حديثو العهد هنا، لقد نُفيوا من العاصمة
What are you looking at?!
إلام تنظرون؟
Get outta here, punks!
غادروا
They fled the capital?
تمّ نفيهم من العاصمة؟
Yeah.
أجل
Only those who produce wealth and show loyalty to the shogun can live in the Flower Capital.
فقط من يكنّون الولاء للشوغن ويجنون المال لهم أحقيّة البقاء في العاصمة
I heard those men were doing some pretty scummy things.
سمعت أنّ أولئك الرجال كانوا يقومون بأمور سيئة هناك
First,
:أولًا
we have Bungo the flunkey.
الوضيع بنغو أيها الأطفال الأوغاد
Night after night, he'd roam the streets setting fires,
كان يضرم الحرائق في البلدة كل ليلة
but he'd bribe officials to avoid punishment.
لكنه لم يكن يُعاقب لأنه يرشي المسؤولين
An arsonist?!
مضرم حرائق؟
Why would he bribe anyone to commit arson?
ما الهدف من إضرام الحرائق؟
Someone else was profiting from those fires.
كان هنالك من يجني المال من ذلك
Enter the man who sold the wood for rebuilding those houses:
إنه تاجر أخشاب يبيع الخشب لإعادة بناء المنازل
That would be Bongo.
اسمه بونغو
That's not all.
لم ننتهي بعد
Yet another targeted those who mourned the loss of family in the fires,
كان الرجل الثالث يستغل الذين ما زالوا ينتحبون على موتاهم في الحريق
extorting large sums of money from them.
ويرغمهم على دفع مبالغ باهظة
Meet Bingo, a priest and undertaker.
إنه راهب وصانع توابيت يدعى بينغو
No! So those three...
...أتحاولين القول أنّ هؤلاء الثلاثة
That's right. Bingoh, Bongoh, and Bungoh were in cahoots.
أجل، بينغو وبونغو وبنغو كانوا يتعاونون معًا
I knew it.
توقعت ذلك
They're horrible!
هذا فظيع
You're not wrong. But no matter what evil they committed,
صحيح، لكن لا يهم كم اقترفوا من جرائم
they'd buy off officials to avoid any charges.
كانوا يرشون المسؤولين وينجون من الاعتقال
They'd put on a good face in public,
ويتظاهرون أنهم أشخاص طيبون
but they're actually the worst kind of people.
لكنهم أقذر الأشخاص
But here's the thing.
...والأمر الطريف
Interestingly enough, Oiran Komurasaki, that beautiful girl who died yesterday,
وقع ثلاثتهم في حب الأويران كوموراساكي، الفتاة الجميلة التي ماتت البارحة
All three spent so much money on her that they went broke!
وأنفقوا مالًا كثيرًا عليها حتى أفلسوا
The gods were watching after all! And them's the rumors!
إنّ الآلهة ترعانا برحمتها فعلًا وهذه هي الإشاعات
That's a good story.
يا لها من قصة
But... aren't those rumors a bit too specific?
لكن هذه تفاصيل دقيقة جدًّا على أن تكون مجرد إشاعات
It's all true, isn't it?
لا بدّ أنها حقيقية
If so, that means the oiran tricked them on purpose!
هذا يعني أنّ تلك الأويران تعرف من يكونون وخدعتهم
Impressive.
هذا مذهل
Who was Komurasaki really?
من تكون كوموراساكي؟
Hey, those are the guys!
صحيح، إنهم هم
That's right! I saw them!
هكذا إذًا، لقد تذكرت
They made a scene during the oiran's procession.
كانوا يحدثون جلبة أثناء موكب الأويران
Yasu took them in and provided a place for them to live,
وفّر ياسو-سان مكان يعيشوا فيه واهتمّ بهم
but they're still acting all high and mighty.
لكن ما زالوا يتصرفون بغطرسة
Tonoyasu really likes taking care of others. Even jerks like them!
تونوياسو رجل طيب فعلًا، حتى مع الحثالة أمثالهم
I'm certain this symbol inspired a great many people!
أنا واثق أنّ كثيرًا تحفّزوا برؤية هذه المنشورات
Be sure to tell young Kin'emon and the others:
أخبروا كينيمون-كن والبقية رجاءً
We'll fight alongside you no matter what!
أخبروهم أننا سنقاتل إلى جانبكم مهما كلف الأمر
Young Kin'emon?!
كينيمون"-كن"؟
It brought me joy to see you two again!
أنا سعيد لرؤيتكما أيضًا
Now, it's time to get to work!
والآن، لدي بعض الأعمال
Hey, wait!
مهلًا يا عم
You know, lots of people will die in the week leading up to the great battle!
من المرجح أن يموت الكثير في الأيام التي تسبق المعركة النهائية
So if you'll excuse me!
لذلك أستأذن منكم
The ladies' man!
رجل وسيم
The classy dame!
وامرأة حسناء
And the girl next door!
وسيدة راقية
It was good to see you all!
سررت بلقائكم جميعًا
So, who was that old man?
من يكون هذا العجوز إذًا؟
I listened in but didn't quite catch what his relationship is with you two.
لم أستطع معرفة العلاقة التي تربطكم
Ditto.
ولا أنا
Yes, Tonoyasu's really friendly. But who is he?
أجل، بدا لي رجلًا مبتهجًا، من يكون تونوياسو-سان؟
The two of us...
...نحن كذلك
...have no idea!
لا فكرة لدينا
You have no idea?!
ماذا تقصدان؟
You kept talking to him without knowing who he is?!
كنتما تحدثانه دون أدنى معرفه عنه؟
Well, he just kept going on and on...
لقد استمر في الكلام دون توقف
How could anyone forget such a quirky guy?!
كيف أمكنكما نسيان أمر شخص مثله؟
He addressed us as "young Kanjuro" and "little Shinobu,"
..."بما أنه كان يدعونا بـ"كن" و"تشان
so I thought it rude to ask if he had once been someone important.
فكرتُ أنه إن كان شخصًا مهمًّا في الماضي، فسيكون من الفظاظة أن نسأله
He was so casual, so perhaps he's a childhood friend?
كان يتحدث معكما بكل راحة، لربما يكون صديق طفولة؟
Or a teacher? An older schoolmate maybe?
أم معلّمًا من نوع ما؟ أو زميلًا أكبر سنًّا؟
Who is he?!
من يكون؟
You bastards!
أيها الوغدان
Get 'em, Madilloman!
عليك بهما يا ماديلومان
Hold tight, gramps!
تمسك جيدًا أيها العجوز
You call it haki, but in Wano we refer to it as ryuo.
ما تدعوه بـ"هاكي" ندعوه "ريو" في بلاد وانو
"Ryuo"...?
ريو؟
It means "to flow."
"إنها كلمة تعني "تدفق
I imagine your haki flows through your body, too.
أنا واثق أنّ الهاكي خاصتك يتدفق عبر جسدك أيضًا
You must first feel that flow.
أولًا، اشعر به
Alright!
حسنًا
The haki flows through me...
...أجعل الهاكي يتدفق عبر
Don't force it!
لا تجبره على التدفق
Damn! That's not it!
سحقًا، ليس هو
Don't strain yourself!
لا يجب أن تجبره على التدفق
Allow the unused haki in your body to flow to your fist!
اسمح للهاكي الغير مستعمل في جسدك بالتدفق إلى قبضتك
Straw Hat!
قبعة القش
You're a goner!
اختفِ
That's not it!
ليس هو
That's not it, either!
وليس هو أيضًا
Damn!
سحقًا
That's not it! That's not it!
ليس هو، ليس هو
Dammit! Where is it?!
...سحقًا، أين هو
My haki!
الهاكي خاصتي؟
It won't flow into my fist!
إنه لا يتدفق لقبضتي
Hey, hey, he took down too many of my men, that idiot.
لقد أطاح بعديدٍ من الحمقى
Damn!
سحقًا
Haki won't flow to an angry fist!
لن يتدفق الهاكي إلى قبضة غاضبة
Come on! Who's next?!
من التالي؟
Bring it on!
هلمّوا إلي
Hey there, gramps! How's the abdominal pain?
أيها الجد، أيها الجد، كيف ألم بطنك؟
Oh, Yasu!
هذا أنت يا ياسو-سان
It's not much, but I brought you some millet and water.
هذا ليس بالكثير، لكنني أحضرت لك بعض الدّخن والماء
They'll give you energy!
سيمنحانك الطاقة
You're so kindhearted, Yasu.
يا لك من شخص طيب يا ياسو-سان
What a compliment! It's a joy to be called "kindhearted"!
يا لهذا الثناء، أنا سعيد لوصفك لي بالشخص الطيب
I'll give you two more millet grains!
سأمنحك حصّتين إضافيّتين من الدّخن
See you, gramps!
إلى اللقاء أيها الجد
Hey, it's the granny who sells the seaweed! Do you have enough medicine?
أيتها الجدة المخمرة للعشب البحري، هل لديك أدوية كافية؟
I'm all out, but I feel better already, having seen your face.
لا، لكن رؤيتك فحسب تبهجني
You're such a man-killer!
يا آسرة قلوب الرجال
Oh! Mister, how's the knee?
يا سيدي، كيف حال ركبتك؟
Come play with me, Yasu!
ياسو-سان، لنلعب
Hanko, is your mother getting any better?
هانكو، كيف حال أمك المريضة؟
Osaki, how's the baby?
أوساكي-سان، كيف حال رضيعك؟
Coochy-coo!
أعلى، أعلى
Yasu!
ياسو-سان
Visit with us, too!
تعال لرؤيتنا نحن أيضًا
Here, everyone! Take these!
تفضلوا جميعًا، خذوا هذه
Thanks again!
شكرًا لك كالعادة
That Tonoyasu looks to be rolling in dough.
تونوياسو ذاك رجلٌ كريم حقًّا
No one else is able to hand out food like that.
إنه يوزع الطعام لكل من حوله
It's not what you think.
الأمر ليس كما تظنانه
He gets paid peanuts for the work he does.
العمال هنا يتقاضون أجرًا زهيدًا
His only daughter Toko got sold to the capital and has worked there ever since.
ابنته الوحيدة توكو-تشان بيعت للعاصمة للعمل هناك
She sends most of her earnings to Yasu.
إنها ترسل معظم ما تجنيه إلى ياسو-سان
Toko?
توكو؟
I'm not a man!
لستُ رجلًا
Oh, her!
تلك الفتاة
Toko-chan sends him money,
توكو-تشان ترسل أغلب المال له
but he believes keeping it to himself is a waste.
لكنه يعتقد أنّ الاحتفاظ به لنفسه إهدار
Every day he hands out food to those who can't work,
لذا يقوم بتوزيع الطعام لمن لا يستطيعون العمل كل يوم
though he barely eats anything himself.
حتى لو عنى الأمر أن يبقى بلا طعام
He may look ridiculous, but he's a long-beloved figure in our community.
رغم أنّ تعابيره وحركاته تتسم بالبلاهة
He's a saint.
إنه قدّيسنا
Daddy...
...أبي
Daddy!
أبي
It's bedtime! Go to sleep!
هيا اخلدوا للنوم
Damn!
تبًّا
We gotta wait until tomorrow?!
سأنتظر حتى الغد؟
Let me fight some more!
دعوني أقاتل أكثر
So hungry...
...أنا جائع
You gonna feed me or what?!
ألن تسمحوا لي بالأكل؟
Look at him, barking like some dog.
كفاك نباحًا كالكلب
Shut up and sleep!
اخرس واخلد للنوم
I'll be a mummy by tomorrow!
سأصبح كالمومياء في الغد
May I ask you something, Sir Straw Hat?
أيمكنني سؤالك عن شيء يا فتى قبعة القش؟
What?
ماذا؟
Why would you want to fight Kaido? I heard that you lost to him in Kuri.
لماذا تريد قتال كايدو؟ سمعتُ أنك خسرت أمامه في كوري
These guys are annoying.
هؤلاء عائقٌ لنا
Alright, we're good now.
عظيم، هذا جيّد
Gramps!
أيها العجوز
Have you heard of the Four Emperors?
هل تعرف الأباطرة الأربعة؟
No...
كلا
There are four great pirates called Emperors are in this world...
إنهم أربعة قراصنة عظماء يُعرفون بالأباطرة الأربعة
and Kaido is one of them.
كايدو واحد منهم
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates...
أنا الرجل الذي سيصير ملك القراصنة
so I gotta take them all down!
لذلك عليّ أن أطيح بهم جميعًا
The King of the Pirates?
ملك القراصنة؟
Wasn't Roger one such man?
تقصد أنك ستصبح مثل الرجل روجر؟
You know Gold Roger?!
هل تعرف غولد روجر؟
Yes, from when he came to this country many years ago.
لقد زار بلادنا منذ فترة بعيدة
Oh, Kin'emon said the same thing.
صحيح، ذلك ما قاله كينيمون
What?! Kin'emon?!
ماذا؟ كينيمون؟
How do you know that name?!
كيف تعرف هذا الاسم؟
What's going on?!
ما هذا؟
You're... R-Raizo!
أنت ر-رايزو
Straw Hat...
...قبعة القش
You're...
...أنت
This is Raizo... isn't it?
هذا رايزو، صحيح؟
It is I!
هذا أنا
What's going on with you two?!
ما الذي حدث لكما؟
How are you still alive,
...كيف لا تزال قيد الحياة
Raizo?!
يا رايزو؟
Allow me to explain, Boss Hyogoro.
دعني أشرح لك يا هيوغورو-دونو
– Arrest him!
أنت رهن الاعتقال، أنت رهن الاعتقال
There he is! It's the Witching Hour Boy!
ها هو هناك، فتى ساعة السحر
Give it up!
استسلم
Seize him!
أمسكوه
So that's the truth, Raizo?!
أهذا صحيح يا رايزو؟
It's hard to believe that you are the Boss Hyogoro...!
...أنا لا أصدق أنك هيوغورو-دونو المشهور
This is difficult to fathom.
يصعب تصديق هذا
You are saying you actually crossed through twenty years in time
أتقول أنكم حقًّا سافرتم عبر الزمن في ذلك اليوم المشؤوم قبل عشرين سنة إلى حاضر بلاد وانو؟
That is correct. It was due to Lady Toki's sorcery.
نعم، باستعمال تقنية توكي-ساما السحرية
I can't believe it!
لا أصدق ذلك
I can't believe you, Caribou!
وأنا لا أصدقك يا كاريبو
Oh, don't say that, Straw Hat!
لا تقل ذلك رجاءً يا قبعة القش
What the hell, Raizo?!
ما خطبك يا رايزو؟
You thought you had the keys to my cuffs, but they were actually to his!
ظننتَ أنك تملك مفتاح أصفادي لكنك كنتَ تملك أصفاده هو
All this hate doesn't suit you.
لا تكرهني هكذا
Surely I can help in some way.
قد أكون مفيدًا لك
From now on, I'm your underling!
أنا تابعك ابتداءً من الآن يا سيدي
But, in exchange...
لكن في المقابل
please let me leave with you on your ship.
دعني أرافقكم على سفينتكم عندما تغادرون هذا المكان
Ah, so you can't get home?
إذًا فأنت لا تقدر على العودة لوطنك؟
Please forgive me for my past misdeeds!
اعذرني على شِقاي بالماضي
I'm a changed man!
لقد تغيرت عن ما سبق
Alright. If you've changed, then it's fine.
حسنًا، لا مشكلة طالما أنك تغيرت
Ah, I mean, thank you very much!
شكرًا... جزيلًا لك
Is this some kind of trap?! It scares me how easy that was!
هل هذا فخ من نوع ما؟ إنّ سهولة الأمر تخيفني
Sir Luffytaro, this man uses quite the fascinating sorcery.
لوفيتارو-دونو، لدى هذا الرجل تقنية سحرية مثيرة للاهتمام
He could be useful.
قد يكون مفيدًا لنا
I never knew when to let go...
...من دون استسلام
stubbornly clinging to life...
وبكل طمع تشبثت بالحياة
but it was worth it.
سعيد أنني فعلت ذلك
Boss Hyogoro!
هيوغورو-دونو؟
I was a hair's breadth away.
...كان ذلك وشيكًا
I thought I'd die a miserable death here...
ظننتُ أنني سأموت ميتة بائسة هنا
I had made peace with that.
كنتُ قد تقبلتُ موتي
If not for your timely arrival, I would have died...
لو لم أرك اليوم، لمتُّ جاهلًا بكل هذا
The Red Scabbards yet live?
الأغماد التسعة على قيد الحياة؟
Oden's child, Kozuki Momonosuke, survived?
ابن أودين، كوزكي مومونوسكي حي؟
The fires of rebellion...
...أهذا يعني أنّ شرارة التمرد
Do they continue to burn?!
لم تخمد بعد؟
Raizo! Sir Straw Hat!
رايزو، يا فتى قبعة القش
When it comes to this, even a dotard like me still can contribute!
بما أنّ الأمر آل لهذا المآل فحتى هرِم مثلي يمكنه المساهمة
It would be an honor to join you!
هلّا سمحتما لي بالانضمام رجاءً؟
Oh, this is an unexpected boon!
بالطبع، هذا حليف لم أتصور مقابلته أبدًا
Sir Luffy, this man was once the most highly regarded yakuza in all of Wano!
لوفي-دونو، لقد كان في الماضي أحد أعظم زعماء الياكوزا في بلاد وانو
You mentioned that you have been gathering allies in the Flower Capital?
قلتَ أنكم تجمعون حلفاء في عاصمة الزهور، صحيح؟
Indeed.
نعم
It must have been fate that brought you here to Udon.
لا بدّ أنّ القدر أتى بكما لأودون إذًا
In this labor camp, there are four adjoining mining sites of a similar size to this one.
توجد أربعة مناجم سجناء مجاورة كحجم هذا المنجم
Tens of thousands of prisoners are being held here in Udon!
ثمة عشرات الآلاف من السجناء في أودون
However, not all of them were arrested for theft or violence.
لكن لم يُسجن الجميع بداعي السرقة أو القتل
Most of the prisoners are here for one thing:
...أغلب السجناء هنا
treason against Orochi!
بداعي خيانة أوروتشي
Is that so?! That was an oversight!
صحيح، لماذا لم أفكر في هذا؟
The country's rage has been pooled into this location!
لقد تجمع هنا غضب من أنحاء البلاد
The yakuza bosses who once supported Wano from the shadows are all here.
زعماء الياكوزا الذين دعموا بلاد وانو في الظلال موجودون جميعًا هنا أيضًا
I will speak with them. They will gladly fight for the Kozuki Clan.
سأتحدث إليهم، واثق أنهم سيكونون سعداء للقتال من أجل عشيرة الكوزكي
Also, Raizo, see that cell?
...وأيضًا يا رايزو، في تلك الزنزانة
I am already aware.
أنا أعلم
I briefly spoke with Kawamatsu. I intend to release him first.
سبق وتحدثت مع كاواماتسو، سأطلق سراحه أولًا
I got it.
هكذا إذًا؟
If we smash this place to pieces,
إن حطمتُ هذا المكان
everyone will join our cause?!
فسيتحد الجميع معنا؟
Sir Luffy, you are too loud! It will not be that simple!
لوفي-دونو، صوتك مرتفع جدًّا، الأمر ليس بتلك السهولة
Alright! With that decided, bring us some food!
حسنٌ، تمّ تجهيز خطتنا، أحضر لي شيئًا آكله
Please...
...دعوني
feed me.
...أتناول
I'm hungry... and sleepy.
...أنا جائعة... وأشعر بالنعاس
Are we close to the oshiruko, Okiku?
ألم نصل إلى الأوشيروكو بعد يا أوكيكو-تشان؟
The sharkodile is also exhausted, but we have already reached Udon.
الوانيزامي-سان متعب أيضًا لكننا دخلنا مقاطعة أودون سلفًا
Udon Wilderness
برية مقاطعة أودون
Wait for me,
...انتظرني
my sweet oshiruko!
يا أوشيروكو
Is it okay that we're here?
أهذه فكرة جيدة حقًّا؟
Oh, it's good!
لذيذ
Another bowl!
المزيد
Oshiruko!
...أوشيروكو
Extra! Extra! Breaking news!
أخبار عاجلة
The great thief of the Flower Capital,
...اللص فتى ساعة السحر الشهير الذي تسبب بمشكلات في عاصمة الزهور
Flower Capital
عاصمة الزهور
has finally been caught!
قد ألقي عليه القبض أخيرًا
Shogun Orochi!
أوروتشي-ساما
My lord, I have some news you should hear.
أوروتشي-ساما، ثمة أمر أريد إطلاعك عليه
It is about the Witching Hour Boy, who was apprehended the other day.
إنه يخص فتى ساعة السحر الذي قُبض عليه البارحة
Be silent!
اخرس
Have you no sense of how I feel, having lost the love of my life?!
جميعكم لا يفهم ألم فقدان المحبوب
I have only the deepest of sympathies for the passing of Oiran Komurasaki...
إنني أتعاطف معك من كل قلبي بشأن موت الأويران كوموراساكي
But with all due respect, my lord...
لكن وبكل احترام
Kyoshiro's decision was most prudent.
كان قرار كيوشيرو صائبًا
If we let anyone who opposes the shogun live,
إن سُمح لشخص وقف في وجهك بمواصلة العيش
it could undermine His Excellency's authority and prestige.
لقلّل ذلك من سلطتك وسمعتك
My lord...!
أوروتشي-ساما
I couldn't care less about the Witching Hour Boy...
لا أهتم لأمر فتى ساعة السحر
Komurasaki... No other woman could match her beauty.
لا توجد امرأة أخرى بجمال كوموراساكي
Do you not understand that?!
ألا يمكنك إدراك ذلك؟
Thank you for the honor of your presence, Shogun Orochi.
من الجيد جدًّا رؤيتك يا أوروتشي-ساما
But I beg you, please hear me out.
استمع لي رجاءً
The Witching Hour Boy was not your run-of-the-mill thief.
فتى ساعة السحر لم يكن مجرد لص وضيع
He was a cowardly burglar who wreaked havoc throughout the Flower Capital.
إنه اللص الجبان الذي أحدث الفوضى في عاصمة الزهور
He stole from the rich and gave to the poor,
إنه يدعي البطولية بفعل أمور خبيثة كسرقة المال والأغراض ويعطيها الفقراء
He is currently in custody at Rasetsu Prison.
إننا نحتجزه في معقل سجناء بلدة راسيتسو
His true identity is...
...حقيقة هويته هي
What?!
ماذا؟
It's him!
...أهو
H-He... lives?!
أ-أهو لا يزال حيًّا؟
No! I cannot believe it!
محال، لا أصدق هذا
It's him!
...إنه
You are of the Kurozumi Clan? Why did you hide it?
أنت من عشيرة الكوروزومي إذًا؟ لماذا لم تخبرني؟
It's him! It's him!
...إنه... إنه
My lord? My lord?!
سيدي، يا سيدي
What shall we do about the Witching Hour Boy?
ماذا نفعل بشأن لص ساعة السحر؟
Isn't it obvious?!
أليس واضحًا؟
Execute him! Make a public example out of him!
أعدموه، أظهروا إعدامه للعموم ليكون عبرة
Illuminate the light scrolls across Wano immediately!
شغلوا حلازين لفائف الضوء في كل أنحاء بلاد وانو في الحال
They already stand at the ready.
تمّ تجهيز حلازين لفائف الضوء مسبقًا
Kyoshiro!
كيوشيرو
Today, Komurasaki's public funeral will also take place in the capital.
ستُعقد اليوم جنازة كوموراساكي في عاصمة الزهور
Large, grieving crowds hold the potential for disorderly conduct...
الحشود الكبيرة المجتمعة في مكان واحد يكون سلوكها فوضوي
so I have made preparations.
لهذا السبب قمنا باستعداداتنا مسبقًا
That's my Kyoshiro!
كما عهدناك
What are your orders, my lord?
ماذا نفعل الآن؟
I've made up my mind.
حسنًا، حُسم الأمر
We will have the Witching Hour Boy join Komurasaki in death.
سنجعل فتى ساعة السحر يتبع كوموراساكي إلى القبر
He'll be an offering at Komurasaki's funeral!
سيكون عبرة مثل كوموراساكي
Yes, my lord.
صحيح
It's sadly poetic to have the capital's two biggest stars share the stage in death!
خسارة أشهر اثنين في العاصمة في نفس الوقت لهو أمر مثير للسخرية
That is exactly the stroke of genius I expect of my shogun.
هذا ما كنتُ أتوقعه من الشوغن العظيم
I, too, will attend.
سأكون حاضرًا أيضًا
I will witness his execution to the end! I need a palanquin now!
سأشهد على إعدامه، أحضروا المحفّة
Udon's Prisoner Mining Camp
منجم سجناء أودون
It can't be!
هذه كذبة
I can't deal with these bad jokes in the morning, Kaido.
توقف عن قول هذه الدعابات في هذا الصباح الباكر يا كايدو-سان
It's not a joke.
إنها الحقيقة
No... It can't be!
لا يمكن، هذا مستحيل
If you don't believe me, connect a light-scroll snail and see for yourself!
إن ظننت أنني أكذب، فشغل حلزون لفافة الضوء خاصتك
No!
مستحيل
My Komurasaki!
كوموراساكي-تان
He found out Komurasaki died.
لقد عرف بموت كوموراساكي
Queen's gonna be in a bad mood for a while.
سيكون في مزاج سيئ لفترة
This is bad. What should we do?
هذا سيئ، ماذا نفعل؟
Hey, balloon!
أيها البالون
Hurry and get out here!
تعال بسرعة
Shut up! I don't have time for your nonsense!
اخرس، لا وقت لدي لهذا الآن
Hey, balloon! When are we gonna start today's sumo match?
أيها البالون، متى نبدأ نزالات السومو اليوم؟
Don't waste my time!
لا تضيع وقتي
Did you guys get fat overnight or something?!
كيف ازداد وزنكما في ليلة وضحاها؟
No, we didn't! It's just your imagination!
لم يزد، أنت تتخيل فحسب
O-Oh. I see.
هل نخبره أنّ الأوشيروكو اختفى بالأمس؟
Anyway, that's not important right now!
هذا لا يهم الآن
No way! What would Queen do if he heard more bad news?!
مستحيل، قد تقوده صدمة أخرى للجنون
Good point.
أوافقك
But I wonder where the red-bean soup went...
لكن أتساءل أين اختفى الأوشيروكو
This is precisely why I warned Sir Luffy not to eat too much...
لهذا السبب أخبرتُ لوفي-دونو ألّا يأكل كثيرًا
Eating every last drop of oshiruko soup was just excessive!
إنّ تناوله لكل الأوشيروكو في القِدر كان أكثر من اللازم
How does an idiot like him stay alive?
كيف لأحمق مثله أن ينجو؟
More importantly, it's sumo time! Sumo!
المهم الآن هو أن نخوض نزال السومو
Let's go! Dosukoi!
هيا، دوسكوي
I don't have time for idiots. I gotta know the truth!
لا وقت لدي للتعامل مع أحمق مثلك، عليّ اكتشاف الحقيقة
Hey, get me a video feed of the Flower Capital now!
أنت، دعني أرى عاصمة الزهور الآن
Ready the light-scroll snail!
جهزوا حلزون لفيفة الضوء
The light-scroll snail is set!
حلزون لفيفة الضوء جاهز
Show me the Flower Capital.
صلوه بعاصمة الزهور
A video transponder snail?
حلزون بث مرئي؟
What? So that's the Flower Capital.
ماذا؟ لا بدّ أنّ تلك هي عاصمة الزهور
Mount Atama, Kuri
جبل أتاما في كوري
Mount Atama Thieves,
لصوص جبل أتاما
how dare you scum steal all of my food and weapons!
كيف يجرؤون على سرقة طعامي وأسلحتي؟
Let's settle this here and now!
لننهِ الأمر
I'll give you a taste of my trick sword!
إليكم هجوم سيفي الملتهب
I'll devastate Mount Atama!
أنا هنا لتدمير جبل أتاما
This is the end of the Mount Atama Thieves.
هذه هي نهاية مجموعة لصوص جبل أتاما
It's too late! The fire is spreading fast!
لا فائدة، النيران تنتشر بسرعة
There's no extinguishing it, Shutenmaru!
من المستحيل إخمادها يا شوتينمارو-سان
That bastard Holdem!
سحقًا لهولديم
Head to Bakura Town!
لنذهب لبلدة باكورا
Bakura Town?! We'll have to contend with Kaido's forces!
بلدة باكورا؟ سيسعى جيش كايدو خلفنا
So what?!
وماذا في ذلك؟
I'll crush them all!
سأوسعهم ضربًا جميعًا
An Abandoned Village in Kuri
بلدة مهجورة في كوري
I see. I feel sorry for what is happening to Ashura Doji.
هكذا إذًا، أشعر بالأسى على أشورا دوجي
Mm-hm... But we did it for the greater good.
نعم، لكن كان ذلك أفضل خيار
It was unavoidable.
ما باليد حيلة
We'll head to Bakura Town.
لنذهب لبلدة باكورا
Our plan was foiled, and we have no solution in sight.
لقد أُحبطت خطتنا، ولا نعلم ما العمل بعد
For now, we'll get Ashura to see the Beast Pirates as his enemy.
نحتاج أن نجعل أشورا يكن العداء نحو قراصنة الوحوش حاليًّا
His joining us is crucial to our cause!
إنه رجل نحتاج لعونه بكل تأكيد
Ringo's Northern Cemetery
المقبرة الشمالية في رينغو
Here I am... Wh-Wh-What?!
...لقد عدت
Who is this?! What is this?!
من هذا؟ ماذا يحدث؟
Wh-Wh-What's the story here?!
ما-ما-ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
Brook? What's wrong with you? Why are you here? Hm?
بروك؟ ماذا هناك؟ لماذا أنت هنا؟
Zoro, my eyes are popping out of my skull just seeing you like that!
زورو-سان، عيناي خرجتا من مكانهما لرؤيتك هكذا
I'm a skeleton, though, so having eyes isn't really my thing!
رغم أنني لا أملك عينان
So sorry for the interruption!
أعتذر على المقاطعة
Hey, don't get the wrong idea! Get back in here!
مهلًا، لا تسئ الفهم، عد إلى هنا
Oh? Well, okay... If it's no trouble, I'd be happy to.
ماذا؟ حسنًا، إن أردت ذلك
Wow, I'm smitten!
فاتنة
If you would be so obliged, may I see your panties?
أتسمحين لي برؤية ملابسك الداخلية؟
A ghost!
شبح
Wait, he's with me!
مهلًا، لا داعي للخوف منه
I'm so hungry... A curse on you!
أنا جائع، سألعنكم
How scary!
أنا خائفة
Kin'emon tasked me with saying that around here.
أخبرني كينيمون-سان أن أبقى هنا وأردد ذلك
Oh, I see.
إذًا فلهذا السبب هنالك عديدًا من القربان في المدخل
At any rate, it's hard to believe you're Momonosuke's little sister.
لكنني لا أصدق أنكِ أخت مومونوسكي-سان
You're as beautiful as an oiran.
أنتِ بنفس جمال الأويران
She sure is. I mean, she is an oiran.
فعلًا، وهذا لأنها أويران أصلًا
I'm jealous, Zoro. How'd you get someone like this to tend to you?!
لا بدّ أنه من اللطيف وجود شخص مثلها بجانبك
I just went to sleep. That's all.
...كنت نائمًا فحسب، لكنها
I am so sorry. You just looked like you were cold.
أعتذر، ظننت أنك تشعر بالبرد
Truth be told, everyone gets love-struck lying next to me!
لكن الرجال يتوقون للنوم بجانبي
Did you like it? No, certainly you loved it!
هل أعجبك ذلك؟ كلا، واثقة أنه أعجبك
Awful straightforward of you...!
أنتِ مبتهجة هذا الصباح
Of course!
نعم
Anyway, I have no idea where Nami and the others went.
على أي حال، أتساءل أين نامي-سان والبقية
Yesterday, they went to the bathhouse,
لقد ذهبن إلى الحمام الساخن، لكن لم أستطع إيجادهنّ هناك
Oh, that reminds me. The Flower Capital is in an absolute frenzy.
صحيح، إنّ عاصمة الزهور في فوضى عارمة الآن
I heard that today is the funeral for Komurasaki, Wano's most beautiful oiran.
سمعتُ أنّ اليوم جنازة كوموراساكي-سان الأويران الأكثر جمالًا في بلاد وانو
Plus, they caught the Witching Hour Boy, the master thief who shared his spoils with the poor!
وقُبض على اللص فتى ساعة السحر الشهير الذي يوزع المال على الفقراء والجميع يتحدث عن ذلك
Ther Witching Hour Boy?! But he couldn't have!
فتى ساعة السحر؟ محال
But it's true.
إنها الحقيقة
Look, it's right here on this broadsheet.
انظري، مكتوب على هذا المنشور
It says that he will be executed in the capital today. They even discovered his true identity.
سيتم إعدامه في العاصمة اليوم، وقد كشفوا عن هويته
He seems to be well known in Ebisu Town...
أعتقد أنه معروف في بلدة إبيسو
You said Ebisu Town?!
أقلت بلدة إبيسو؟
Yes, his name was something like...
...نعم، وقد كان اسمه
I'm fairly sure it was something like Yasu...
ياسو أو ما شابه
Tonoyasu?!
تونوياسو؟
Ah, yes, that's him.
نعم، نعم، هذا اسمه
Toko!
توكو
Hey, what's wrong?!
مهلًا، ما الخطب؟
Wait, Toko!
انتظري يا توكو
Thank you for yesterday. I will be forever in your debt.
شكرًا على إنقاذي البارحة، لن أنسى لطفك ما حييت
Wait, you idiot!
انتظري يا حمقاء
You couldn't even protect her yesterday!
لم تستطيعي حمايتها البارحة
Whaaat?! I only just made it back here!
ماذا؟ لقد عدت توًّا
Wait for me! Hey, you guys!
انتظروني رجاءً تمهلوا
Daddy...
...أبي
Hey, get up.
أنت، لقد حان الوقت
You're here to escort me? How nice of you...
ماذا؟ أتيتم لاصطحابي؟ يا لكرمكم
It... It can't be.
...مـ-مستحيل
He looks like...
...ذلك الرجل
Where are you going?! They want your head!
أين تعتقدين نفسكِ ذاهبة؟ حياتكِ في خطر
Let me go! I need to go!
أفلتني
Hey, pull it together!
مهلًا، تمالكي نفسك
Let me go!
أفلتني
What's going on?!
ما الذي يحدث؟
Toko!
توكو
They're gonna execute him!
سوف يعدمونه
Let me go!
دعني أذهب
They're gonna kill him!
سوف يقتلونه
He's my daddy!
إنه أبي
Toko...
...توكو
What'd you say?!
ماذا قلتِ؟
Looks like another beautiful day in the Flower Capital...
يبدو أنّ اليوم سيكون يومًا جميلًا في عاصمة الزهور